老爸要我们继续他的遗志 救助他人
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off, saving people…
猎杀恶魔 家族事业
hunting things, the family business.
有人在吗？
Anybody here?
不准动
Don't move.
- 萨姆？迪恩？- 妈妈 你认识他们？
- Sam? Dean? - Mom, you know these guys?
我想他们是约翰·温彻斯特的孩子
Yeah, these are John Winchester's boys.
嘿 我是埃伦 那是我女儿乔
Hey, I'm Ellen. My daughter Jo.
你不是再想再打我一拳吧
Gonna hit me again?
你打电话给我们父亲说你可以帮忙
You called our dad. Said you'd help.
- 帮什么忙？- 当然是有关魔鬼的事
- Help with what? - The demon.
你是谁？你是怎么知道的？
Who are you? How do you know?
嘿 我只是开客栈的 但捕猎者都会经过这里
I just run a saloon. Hunters have been known to pass through now and again.
很久以前你父亲也是如此 约翰 就像这家里的一份子
Including your dad, a long time ago. John was like family once.
- 你认为父亲和埃伦以前在一起过吗？- 不可能
- You think Dad and Ellen had a thing? - No way.
那为什么他不告诉我们关于她的事
Then why didn't he tell us about her?
- 你妈怎么会牵扯进来的？- 我父亲
- How'd your mom get into this stuff? - My dad.
他也是个猎捕者 但已经过世了
He was a hunter. He passed away.
- 我能帮忙 - 我知道你能
- I could help. - I'm sure you could.
- 但你妈妈可能会杀了我 - 你害怕我妈妈？
- But I think your mother might kill me. - You're afraid of my mother?
我想是的
I think so.
我检查过保险丝了 没有坏
I checked the fuses, they're fine.
是电线的问题
It's the wiring.
听着 你向我保证 在我搬进来时一切都会安顿好的
Look, you promised this place would be ready when I moved in.
不行 你现在就要来
No, you come up now.
求你了
Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
真恶心
Gross.
什么鬼东西？
What the hell?
[邪恶力量 第2季第6集]
洛杉矶 加利福尼亚
Los Angeles, California.
在洛杉矶发生了什么事？
What's in L.A.?
有人用一种魔鬼仪式 绑架了一个年轻女孩
Young girl's been kidnapped by an evil cult.
是吗？
Yeah?
- 这女孩叫什么？- 凯蒂·赫尔姆斯
- Girl got a name? - Katie Holmes.
真是有趣 你什么时候变得八卦了
That's funny. And for you, so bitchy.
或者 去瞧瞧母女吵架
Whereas on the other hand, catfight.
我是你的母亲 对你不需要讲道理
I don't have to be reasonable!
- 你不能把我拴在这 - 你想试试吗 宝贝
- You can't keep me here. - Don't you bet on that.
你想怎样 把我拴在地下室吗？
What are you gonna do, chain me up in the basement?
你想的比那更糟糕
You've had worse ideas than that.
你不想待在这儿吗？那就不要了 回学校去
You don't wanna stay, don't. Go back to school.
我不属于那里 在那我是个收集刀子的怪胎
I didn't belong there. I was a freak.
在肮脏的后巷被杀 这就是你的归属吗？
Yeah, but getting yourself killed on a back road, that's where you belong?
伙计们 来的不是时候
Guys, bad time.
- 知道 女士 - 10点之前我们很少喝酒的
- Yes, madam. - Yeah, we rarely drink before 10 anyway.
等等 我想知道他们对此有什么想法
Wait. I wanna know what they think about this.
我不在乎他们怎么想
I don't care what they think.
这里营业吗？
Are you guys open?
- 是的 - 不
- No! - Yes!
我们还是到对面的Arby的快餐店吧
We'll just check out the Arby's down the road.
哈维酒馆
Harvelle's.
是的 牧师
Yeah, Preacher.
三周前一名年轻的女孩 在费城的一间公寓里失踪了
Three weeks ago, a young girl disappears from a Philadelphia apartment.
- 拿着 这不会咬人 - 是的 它不咬人 但你妈会
- Take it, it won't bite. - No, but your mom might.
这女孩不是第一个失踪的女孩
This girl wasn't the first.
在过去的80年里有6名女孩失踪了
Over the past 80 years, six women have vanished…
在同一栋楼里 而且都是金发
all from the same building, all blonds.
只是每10或20年才发生一次 所以警察对此并没有在意
Only happens every decade or two, so cops never eyeball the pattern.
所以凶手要么是一个老年连环杀手
We're either dealing with a serial killer
这些东西是谁整理的？阿什？
Who put this together? Ash?
我自己理的
I did it myself.
我得承认 我们一路上查的都是小案子
I gotta admit, we hit the road for a lot less.
- 很好 如果你喜欢 这案子就归你们了 - 妈妈
- Good. You like the case so much, take it. - Mom
乔安娜？贝思家失去的已经够多了
Joanna Beth, this family has lost enough.
我不想再失去你
I won't lose you too.
就是不想
I just won't.
抢走乔的案子让我有些不安
I feel kind of bad, snaking Jo's case.
是吧 也许是她更适合做文书工作
Well, maybe she put together a good file…
但你有没有见过她出去做过？
but could you see her out here working one of these things?
我想是没干过
I don't think so.
有什么发现吗？
Getting anything?
没 还没有
No, not yet.
那是什么？
What's that?
什么？
What?
不会吧
Holy crap.
那是空灵物
That's ectoplasm.
萨姆 我知道 我们要对付的是什么东西了
Well, Sam, I think I know what we're dealing with here.
这可是个大家伙
It's the Stay Puft Marshmallow Man.
迪恩 这样的东西我只见过两次
Dean, I've only seen this stuff, like, twice.
我的意思是 能留下这样的东西 这恶灵的厉气一定不小
I mean, to make this stuff, you have to be one majorly pissed - off spirit.
那在他把更多的女孩藏起来之前 先抓住这个鬼东西
All right, let's find this badass before he snags any more girls.
是的 这房子不错
It's so convenient.
我把它修的很好了 所有的房间都有家俱
Fixed it up real nice. Apartments come furnished too.
真是太空旷了
It is so spacious.
我朋友一定要让我来看看这里
My friend told me that I had to come check it out.
我得说他是对的 这里真的很不错
And I have to admit that she was right.You did a really good job with this place.
- 你在这里做什么？- 是你啊 亲爱的
- What the hell are you doing here? - There you are, honey.
这是我的男朋友迪恩和他的弟弟萨姆
This is my boyfriend Dean and his buddy Sam.
很高兴见天你 你找到个好女孩
Good to meet you. Quite a gal you got here.
是的 她很火
Oh, yeah, she's a pistol.
那你们看过公寓了吗？
So did you already check out the apartment?
- 那个要租的公寓 - 是的 我们很喜欢 不错
- The one for rent. - You bet. Yes. Loved it. Great flow.
- 你们怎么进来的？- 门是开着的
- How'd you get in? - It was open.
艾德 上一个住客是什么时候搬出去的？
Now, Ed, um, when did the last tenant move out?
嗯 大约一个月前
Uh, about a month ago.
也是不知所踪 害我还要再把它租出去
Cut and run too. Stiffed me for the rent.
是啊 那是她的损失 我们赚到了
Well, her loss, our gain.
只要迪恩喜欢 我就满足了
Because if Dino loves it, it's good enough for me.
喔 亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
我们租了
We'll take it.
好的
Okay.
- 我帮你拍软沙发了 - 你妈知道你在这里吗？
- I'll flip you for the sofa. - Does your mother know you're here?
- 我跟她说我去维加斯了 - 你认为她会吃你这一套？
- Said I was going to Vegas. - She'll buy that?
我可不是白痴 我让阿什在信用卡上动手脚
I'm not an idiot. I got Ash to lay a credit card
让人觉得我是在去赌城的路上
trail straight to the casinos.
你不应该对你妈妈说谎
You know, you shouldn't lie to your mom.
也不应该出现在这儿
You shouldn't be here either.
我已经在这了 所以不要不爽了 认了吧
Well, I am, so untwist your boxers and deal with it.
对了 那些钱你是从哪弄来的？
Where'd you get all that money, anyways?
- 在客栈打工得来的 - 捕猎者出手可不会那么大方
- Working. - Hunters don't tip that well.
那他们也不那么会打牌
Well, they aren't that good at poker either.
- 谁？- 她和你在一起吗？
- Yeah. Is she with you?
喔 嗨 埃伦
Oh, hi, Ellen.
她留了个纸条说去维加斯了 我根本不相信她的话
She left a note she's in Vegas. I don't believe it.
- 你敢说？- 我就说
- Don't tell her. - I'm telling her.
- 我会杀了你 - 你不会的
- You're not supposed to be here.
迪恩
Dean?
- 我没见过她 - 你确定？
- Haven't seen her. - You sure?
是的 我确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
那好 如果她出现 你就把她给拖回来？
Please, if she shows up, you'll drag her back here, won't you?
- 那是当然 - 好了 谢谢
- Absolutely. - Okay. Thanks, honey.
这地方是1924年建的
This place was built in 1924.
这里本来是仓库
It was originally a warehouse…
几个月前改建成公寓的
converted into apartments a few months ago.
是吗？那在1924年之前这里有什么？
Yeah, what was here before 1924?
什么也没有 一块空地
Nothing. Empty field.
最大的可能性是 有人惨死在那座房子里
So most likely scenario, someone died bloody in the building…
现在他的灵魂又回来作祟了
now he's back and raising hell.
我已经查过了
Already checked.
过去82年里 没有任何暴力死亡事件
In the past 82 years, zero violent deaths.
除非清洁工在湿地板上滑倒的事也算
Unless you count a janitor who slipped on a wet floor.
你能坐下吗？
Would you sit down, please?
你查过警察局的纪录 和郡里的死亡纪录了吗？
So have you checked police reports, county death records?
讣告 验尸房报告 以及其他信息来源
Obituaries, mortuary reports and seven other sources.
- 我知道自己该怎么做 - 我想还有漏网之鱼吧
- I know what I'm doing. - Think the jury's still out on that one.
你能不能把刀放下？
Could you put the knife down?
好吧 那么 有可能是别的什么
Okay, so, uh, it's something else, then.
也许是某个被诅咒的物品 有灵魂附在上面
Maybe some cursed object that brought a spirit with it.
我们得把整座大楼扫描一遍 是吗？
We gotta scan the building, everywhere we can get to, right?
是的 你和我负责最上面的两层楼
Right. So you and me will take the top two floors.
还是分开行动比较快
We'd move faster if we split up.
哦 这可由不得你
Well, this isn't negotiable.
那你打算请我吃晚餐吗？
So you gonna buy me dinner?
你这话是什么意思
What are you talking about?
如果你想钓我的话 最好是请我吃饭
If you're gonna ride me this close, it's only decent you buy me dinner.
这也太荒唐了
Oh, that's hilarious.
骗你妈就已经够糟糕的了
It's bad enough I lied mom
你还以为我会让你离开我的视线吗
but if you think I'm letting you out of my sight…
不知道你有没有注意到 那恶灵喜欢你这种类型的
Don't know if you've noticed, but you're the spirit's type.
一点没错
Exactly.
你想自己当诱饵？
You wanna be bait?
这可是引它出来最快捷的办法 你知道的
Quickest way to draw it out and you know it.
- 什么？- 我真后悔
- What? - I'm so regretting this.
我已经受够了你的胡说八道
You know, I've had it up to here with your crap.
- 你说什么 - 你大男子主义的胡说八道
- Excuse me? - Your chauvinist crap.
- 你认为女人干不了这种事情 - 这跟性别没有关系
- You think women can't do the job. - This aingt Gender Studies.
女人当然能做这种事
Women can do the job fine.
菜鸟就不行 你根本没有任何经验
Amateurs can't. You got no experience.
你现在满脑子都是
What you do have is a bunch of half - baked romantic notions…
那些酒鬼灌输给你的半吊子浪漫想法
that some barflies put in your head.
- 你说这话的口气怎么那么象我妈 - 这不好吗？
- Now you sound like my mother. - That's a bad thing?
- 因为我告诉你… - 什么？
- Because let me tell you - What?
算了
Forget it.
- 不行 是你先提起的 - 乔 你还有别的选择
- No, you started this. - Jo, you got options.
没有哪个神志清醒的人会选择这种人生
No one in their right mind chooses this life.
我爸从我小时候就开始训练我了
I started in this when I was so young…
- 我希望当时能有别的选择 - 你喜欢这个工作
- …I wish I could do something else. - You love this.
没错 可我这人有点不正常
Yeah, but I'm a little twisted.
你不觉得我也有点不正常吗？
You don't think I'm a little twisted too?
乔 你有个关心你的妈妈
Jo, you got a mother that worries about you…
她希望你能得到更好的 那些都是好事
who wants something more for you. Those are good things.
你不能把这样的事丢弃
You don't throw things like that away.
丢了就很难再找回来了
Might be hard to find later.
什么？
What?
我不是很肯定
I'm not sure.
你闻到了吗？
You smell that?
什么味道 煤气泄露？
What is that, a gas leak?
不是 是别的什么
No, something else.
我知道那是什么
I know it.
只是叫不出名字
Just can't put my finger on it.
恭喜你刚刚发现了第一个恶灵
Mazel tov. You just found your first spirit.
它躲在通风管道里
It's inside the vent.
拿着
Here.
里面有东西 拿着
There's something in there. Here.
有人留着纪念品呢
Somebody's keeping souvenirs.
老天啊这栋楼真是…
This building, I swear to God.
我得出去
I'm so out of here.
早安 公主
Morning, princess.
- 萨姆在哪里？- 他去买咖啡了
- Where's Sam? - Went to get coffee.
我的腰啊
Ohh, my back.
你在那张大软床上睡得好吗？
How'd you sleep on that big, soft bed?
我没睡 我刚刚把所有的资料重新看了一遍
I didn't. Just been going over everything.
- 拿着这个 - 这是要干吗？
- Here. - What's this for?
这个玩起来 可比你手里的小刀有意思多了
It'll work a lot better than that little pig sticker you're twirling around.
威廉·安东尼·哈维
William Anthony Harvelle.
对不起 我的错
Sorry. My mistake.
什么你…
What do you?
关于你父亲 你记得些什么？
What do you remember about your dad?
第一件出现在你脑海里的事是什么？
I mean, what's the first thing that pops into your head?
别这样 告诉我
Come on, tell me.
我当时才六七岁
I was 6 or 7…
接着 嗯… 他第一次带我去射击
and, uh, he took me shooting for the first time.
打栅栏上的瓶子之类的东西
You know, bottles on a fence, that kind of thing.
我打中了每个瓶子
I bull's eyed every one them.
他笑了 就像…
He gave me this smile, like…
我不知道
I don't know.
他一定很为你骄傲
He must have been proud.
你爸爸呢？
What about your dad?
我父亲去世得时候 我还是个小女孩 但是…
I was still in pigtails when my dad died.
我仍然记得他打猎回来
But I remember him coming home from a hunt.
他推开门 就象… 像史蒂夫·麦奎一样
He'd burst through that door like Steve McQueen or something.
然后把我搂在怀里
And he'd sweep me up in his arms…
我甚至能嗅到他那件旧夹克得皮革味
and I'd breathe in that old leather jacket of his.
而我妈妈又气又哭？
And my mom, who was sour and pissed…
他一走又恢复了笑容
from the minute he left, she started smiling again.
因为我们…
And we were
我们还是一家人
We were a family.
你想知道我为什么干这样的活吗？
You wanna know why I wanna do the job?
为了他
For him.
让我觉得能和他在一起
It's my way of being close to him.
那好 告诉我这难道有错吗？
Now, tell me, what's wrong with that?
没有
Nothing.
- 咖啡在哪儿？- 外头有好多警察
- Where's the coffee? - There are cops outside.
又有一个女孩失踪了
Another girl disappeared.
住在2楼的埃利斯
Theresa Ellis. Apartment 2-F.
她的男朋友今天一早向警局报失踪
Her boyfriend reported her missing around dawn.
那她的公寓怎么样？
And her apartment?
墙上 天花板上到处都是裂缝
Cracks all over the plaster, walls, ceiling.
还有空灵物
There was ectoplasm too.
根据那些东西和那簇头发
Between that and that hair
我觉得那个恶灵是从透过墙进来的
I'd say this sucker's coming from the walls.
可那会是什么东西呢？那栋楼的历史很清白呀
Yeah, but who is it? Building's history is totally clean.
也许是我们看错地方了
Maybe we're looking in the wrong place.
- 你什么意思？- 看看这个
- What do you mean? - Check this out.
- 空地？- 这栋楼就建在这片空地上
- An empty field? - It's where this building was built.
看看它隔壁是什么
Take a look at the one next door.
窗子
The windows.
- 铁条 - 旁边是一所监狱？
- Bars. - We're next door to a prison?
谢谢 阿什 对了 如果你胆敢把这事告诉我妈
Thanks, Ash. And if you breathe a word of this to my mom…
没错 我会的 用钳子
That's right, I will. With pliers.
好吧 Moyamensing监狱 建于1835年 在1963年被推倒
Okay, Moyamensing prison, built in 1835, torn down in 1963.
看看这个 以前他们处决犯人的方式
And get this, they used to execute people…
就是吊死在监狱旁的那块空地上
by hanging them in the empty field next door.
那么 我们需要在那里被处决所有犯人的名单
Well, then, we need a list of all the people executed there.
阿什已经在弄了
Ash is already on it.
有157个名字？
A hundred fifty seven names?
- 我们得把范围缩小一下 - 是的
- We gotta narrow that down. - Yeah.
否则的话真得累死人的
Or else we're gonna be digging up a hell of a lot of stiffs.
赫尔曼 韦伯斯特 马杰特？
Herman Webster Mudgett?
怎么了？
Yeah?
那不是H。-H。- 霍姆斯的真名吗？
Wasn't that H.H. Holmes' real name?
你不是开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
霍姆斯在1896年5月7日于Moyamensing被处死
Yup. Holmes was executed at Moyamensing May 7th, 1896.
H。-H。-霍姆斯本人
H.H. Holmes himself.
- 我是说 这太不可思议了 - 这家伙是谁？
- Come on, I mean, what are the odds? - Who is this guy?
连环杀手这个词是霍姆斯发明的
The term "multi murderer, " they coined it to describe Holmes.
他是美国第一个连环杀手
He was America's first serial killer before
那时还没有人知道连环杀手是什么
anybody knew what that was.
他承认了27宗谋杀 但有人认为受害者至少有100多个
He confessed to 27 murders. Some think over a hundred.
他偏爱的受害者类型是 漂亮纤弱 金发碧眼的女性
And his victim flavor of choice: pretty, petite blonds.
他用氯仿麻醉后再杀了她们
He, uh, used chloroform to kill them.
那就是我昨晚在走廊上闻到的
Which is what I smelled in the hallway last night.
在他的窝里 警察找到了人体的残留物
At his place, cops found human remains…
骨头碎片和血迹斑斑的金色长发
bone fragments and long locks of bloody blond hair.
伙计 他肯定知道怎么选择受害者
Boy, you sure know how to pick them.
我们只要找到他的尸骨 撒上盐烧了就行 对吧？
We just find the bones, salt them and burn them, right?
没那么简单
Well, it's not that easy.
虽然他的尸体葬在镇上
His body is buried in town…
但是那里被好几吨的水泥裹着
but it's encased in a couple tons of concrete.
什么？为什么？
What? Why?
传闻说他不愿任何人去动他的尸体
The story goes that he didn't want anybody mutilating his corpse.
因为 你知道 那是他生前干的事
Because, you know, that's what he used to do.
还有什么？
You know something?
还有个更麻烦的问题
We might have an even bigger problem.
还有什么更麻烦的？
How does this get bigger?
霍姆斯在芝加哥建过一栋公寓楼
Holmes built an apartment building in Chicago.
有人管它叫「杀人小楼」 整个大楼就像个死亡机器
They called it the Murder Castle. The whole place was a death factory.
到处是机关 陷阱和迷烟管
They had trapdoors, acid vats, quicklime pits.
他还造了些密室… 就在墙里面
He built these secret chambers inside the walls.
把受害者关进去 让他们先活上几天
He'd lock his victims in, keep them alive for days.
有些人被他闷死 另一些则被饿死
Some he'd suffocate, others he'd let starve to death.
这么说特丽萨可能还活着 就在这些墙里面
So Theresa could still be alive. She could be inside these walls.
我们需要找些大锤和铁锹来砸碎墙壁
We need sledgehammers, crowbars.
或是任何可以藏得下一个女孩的地方
We gotta smash these walls anywhere thick enough to hide a girl.
好的 检查完东南面的墙后再打给我们
Okay, call us after you check the southeast wall.
萨姆快查完一楼了
Sam's almost done with the first floor.
他还没有找到那个混蛋囚犯
Hasn't found jack squat either.
- 怎么了？- 太窄了过不去
- What is it? - It's too narrow. I can't go any further.
- 让我看看 - 什么 你干嘛… ？
- Let me see. - What. What are you?
- 我得先理理「管子」 - 什么？
- Should have cleaned the pipes. - What?
我得先洗洗管子
I wish the pipes were clean.
闭嘴 我可以过去
Shut up. I can fit in there.
- 不要一个人去那里面 - 你有更好的主意吗？
- You're not going in there by yourself. - You got a better idea?
那个…
The…
- 你在哪？- 到达北面的墙了
Where are you? - By the north wall.
我现在要从一个像是通风管道的地方下去
I'm heading down some kind of air duct.
- 不 不 不 呆在上面 - 我们得救出那个女孩 不是吗？
- No, no, no, stay up here. - Dean, we gotta find this girl, don't we?
我很好
I'm okay.
好吧 我这就过去
All right, I'm heading to you.
该死
Damn it.
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
怎么了？
What is it?
乔？乔？
Jo? Jo?
乔
Jo?
乔？
乔
Jo!
- 他抓走了乔 - 什么？发生什么事了？
- He's got Jo. - What? How'd that happen?
我没有陪着她 让她落单了 该死的
I wasn't with her. I left her alone. Damn it!
- 我们会找到她的 - 去哪找？
- Look, we'll find her. - Where?
- 在墙里面 - 我们已经在了
- Inside the walls. - We've been inside the walls.
没有女孩在那里 她也不在
None of the other girls are there. She won't be either.
先静下来想想 也许我们把霍姆斯的杀人地点想错了
Let's take a beat and think about this. Maybe we got Holmes' m.o. wrong.
那我们得想的快点
Well, we better frigging think fast.
- 你好？- 你说谎 她就在你那
- Yeah. - You lied to me. She's there.
- 埃伦 - 阿什全招了
- Ellen. - Oh, Ash told me everything.
虽然他是个天才 但是说起谎来却像个小孩
He's a genius, but folds like a cheap suit.
快让我女儿听电话
Put my damn daughter on.
她会打回给你的 她 呃 有些女人的事要做
She'll call you back. She's taking care of feminine business.
是啊 她在哪里？
Yeah, right. Where is she?
她在哪里？
Where is she?
- 你瞧 我们会把她带回来的 - 带她回来？从哪里？
- Look, we'll get her back. - Get her back? Back from what?
- 我猎杀的恶灵… 把她抓走了 - 哦 我的天哪
- The spirit we're hunting, it took her. - My God.
- 她会没事的 我保证 - 你保证？
- She'll be okay.I promise. - You promise?
你保证？这不是我第一次 听温彻斯特家的人说这话了
That is not the first time I've heard that from a Winchester.
- 什么？- 如果她有什么三长两短…
- What? - If anything happens to her
不会的 我不会的 埃伦 我真的很抱歉
It won't. I won't let it. Ellen, I'm sorry. I really am.
我现在马上坐第一班飞机过去 几个小时后就到
I'm taking the first flight out. I'll be there in a few hours.
该死的
Damn it!
不要再自责了 迪恩 你也不想的
Don't beat yourself up. There's nothing you could have done.
- 拜托告诉我你发现了什么 - 呃 算是吧
- Tell me you got something. - Uh, maybe.
你瞧
Look.
看看霍姆斯的杀人小楼蓝图
Look at the layout.
那里有墙内的拷问密室 对吧？
There's other torture chambers inside the walls, right?
但是有一个我们没有注意到… 在他的地下室还有一个
But there's one we haven't considered, the one in his basement.
- 但这栋楼没有地下室 - 是的 这里没有 但我刚刚发现
- This building doesn't have a basement. - Right, but I just noticed this.
在下面的地基里 看起来像个废弃的下水道
Beneath the foundation, looks like part of an old sewer system…
- 已经被荒废了… - 我们走
- …that hasn't been used for - Let's go.
有人吗？
Hello?
有… 有人在？
Is anybody there?
你叫特丽萨吗？
Your name's Theresa?
是的
Yes.
也许这么说没有用 但是… 我是来这救你的
This won't make you feel better, but I'm here to rescue you.
哦 天哪 他就在外面 他要来杀我们了
Oh, God. He's out there. He's gonna kill us.
不 他杀不了我们
No, he won't.
我们会逃出去的
We're getting out.
我的朋友正在找我们
My friends are looking for us. They'll find us.
哦 天哪 他来了
Oh, God, he's here!
嘘 小声点
Shh! Just be quiet.
就这里了
Here.
- 准备好了？- 是的
Got it? - Yeah.
你真可爱
You're so pretty.
真漂亮
So beautiful.
下地狱吧
Go to hell.
你喜欢那样吗？
How do you like that?
纯铁的 你个变态混蛋
Pure iron, you creepy ass son of a bitch.
他走了吗？
Is he gone?
我不知道 我…
I don't know. I…
嘿
Hey!
不
NO!
- 乔 - 我在这
- Jo? - I'm here.
快点
Come on!
我来救你出去
We're gonna get you out of here, all right?
萨姆
Sam!
等等
Hang on.
快点
Come on!
- 你还好吗？- 好多了
- You all right? - Been better.
在他回来之前我们快走吧
Let's get out of here before he comes back.
- 事实上 你还不能马上离开这里 - 什么？
- I don't think you're leaving here yet. - What?
记得我说过 由你来当诱饵是个馊主意吗？
Remember when I said you being bait was a bad plan?
现在那是唯一一个办法了
Now it's kind of the only one we got.
就现在
Now.
尽情的叫吧
Scream all you want, you dick…
你是走不出这盐圈的
but there's no way you're stepping over that salt.
那么… 这活有你想像中的那么迷人吗？
So this job as glamorous as you thought it would be?
除了你裤子上的屎尿 是的
Well, except for all the pee your pants terror, yeah, sure.
但是那个叫特丽萨女孩 因为我们活了下来
But that Theresa girl's gonna live a life because of us.
- 这值得的 不是吗？- 是啊 是的 值得
- It's worth it, isn't it? - Yeah. Yeah, it is.
嘿 如果有人再找到这个下水道
Hey, what if somebody finds that sewer?
或者暴雨把那些盐冲走了呢？
Or a storm washes the salt away?
两种可能都有 那也是为什么我们要等会再走了
Both very fine points, which is why we're waiting here.
等什么？
For what?
那个
For that.
你偷了一辆水泥搅拌车？
You ripped off a cement truck?
我会还回去的
I'll give it back.
这就能把他死死地困在下面了
Well, that ought to keep him down there till hell freezes over.
你… 你不会突然骂我吧 会吗？
Boy, you really weren't kidding about flying out, were you?
来点音乐怎样？
How about we listen to some music?
这一路有的受了
This is gonna be a long drive.
埃伦…
Ellen.
这一切都是我的错 好吗？
This is my fault, okay?
我撒了谎 抱歉
I lied to you and I'm sorry.
但是乔做的很不错 她爸爸一定会为她骄傲的
But Jo did good out there. I think her dad would be proud.
不要给我这么说… 你不配
Don't you dare say that. Not you.
我要和我的女儿谈一下 单独
I need a moment with my daughter alone.
你很生气 我能理解
You're angry, I understand.
远远不是生气可以形容的
Angry? Angry doesn't begin to touch it.
让我们好好想想吧
Let's just think about this.
- 一切都很好 我还活着 - 在我丢掉你后就不会了
- Everything's okay. I'm alive. - Not after I'm through with you.
是因为我猎鬼 还是因为别的事？
Is this about me hunting or something?
你竟让那对兄弟把你当诱饵
They used you as bait.
他们就在我后面做掩护
They were there backing me up.
那就是为什么你不是干这活的料
That is why you don't have the sense to do it.
你轻易地把性命交给他们
You're trusting them.
约翰？
John?
我以为你和约翰是朋友
I thought you and John were friends.
- 是的 曾经是 对不起 我不是指… - 妈妈…
- Yeah, we were. I'm sorry, I didn't - Mom.
有什么事你没告诉我？
What aren't you telling me?
- 那么糟吗？- 现在不要
- That bad, huh? - Not right now.
出什么事了？
What happened?
- 嘿 告诉我吧 - 放开我
- Hey, talk to me. - Get off me.
- 对不起 再见了 - 迪恩…
- Sorry. See you around. - Dean.
原来我爸爸在最后一次行动时有个拍档
Turns out my dad had a partner on his last hunt.
好笑的是他一向是单独行动的 那个家伙也是
Funny, he usually worked alone. This guy did too…
但我猜我父亲以为可以信任他
but guess my father figured he could trust him.
结果他错了 那个家伙搞砸了 让我爸送了命
Mistake. The guy screwed up, got my dad killed.
- 这和… - 那个人就是你的老爸 迪恩
- What does this have to do? - It was your father.
什么？
What?
那你觉得约翰为什么再也没回来 再也没和我们说过话？
Why do you think John never came back? Never told you about us?
因为他不敢再面对我的母亲 这就是原因
Because he couldn't look my mom in the eye after that. That's why.
- 乔… - 给我离开这里
- Jo - Just get out of here.
拜托 快走吧
Please, just leave.